[](https://www.bestrandoms.com/)Provide the most powerful random tools
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Submit your ideas

Recommended

* [Random Best Times When Women Called Out Obvious Sexism In 2020](https://www.bestrandoms.com/get-random-best-times-when-women-called-out-obvious-sexism-in-2020)
* [Random Historical Torture Methods Designed To Make The Pain Last As Long As Possible](https://www.bestrandoms.com/get-random-historical-torture-methods-designed-to-make-the-pain-last-as-long-as-possible)
* [Random People Who Fell from Ridiculously High Heights, But Managed To Survive](https://www.bestrandoms.com/get-random-people-who-fell-from-ridiculously-high-heights-but-managed-to-survive)
* [Random Terrifying Scuba Accidents That Will Make You Think Twice About Diving](https://www.bestrandoms.com/get-random-terrifying-scuba-accidents-that-will-make-you-think-twice-about-diving)
* [Random Times The Mandela Effect Seemed To Change Famous Brand Names](https://www.bestrandoms.com/get-random-times-the-mandela-effect-seemed-to-change-famous-brand-names)

Privacy Policy
==============

We value our users’ privacy. When you use our services, we may collect and use information about you. Through this privacy policy, we hope to show you how we might collect and use this information when using our services, and how we can provide you with access to and protection of this information. This privacy policy is closely related to the services you use. Please read it carefully and follow the guidelines of this privacy policy when necessary to make your choice as appropriate. We try to keep the technical terms in this privacy policy brief and provide links to further explanation for your understanding.

By using or continuing to use our services, you consent to the collection, use, storage, and sharing of your information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or related matters, please contact us via [\[email protected\]](https://www.bestrandoms.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**We may collect the following information when you visit the website:**

Log Information is technical information that the system may automatically collect through beacon cookies, web cookies, or other means when you use our services, including:

Device or software information, such as configuration information provided by your mobile device, web browser, or other program used to access our service, your Ip address, and the version and device identifier used by the mobile device;

The information you search for or browse when using our service, such as the web search terms you use, the URL of the social media page you visit, and other information and content details you browse or request when using our service;

#### Log Files

We don't use log files, but we use the third-party statistical plug-in StatCounter, like many other Web sites, StatCounter may use log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies

BestRandoms does use cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, record the user specific information, such as the web content just obtained, so as to compare with the web content obtained next time, and save it in the user's browser so that the user can get it directly next time.

**How we might use information**

We may use the information gathered in the course of our service to you for the following purposes:

To provide services to you;

We provide services for authentication, customer service, security, fraud detection, archiving, and backup purposes, to ensure the security of our products and services to you;

Help design new services and improve our existing website;

To provide you with more relevant advertising to replace general advertising;

Evaluate and improve the effectiveness of advertising and other promotional and promotional activities in our services;

Website certification or management of website upgrades;

To get you involved in the investigation of our website and services.

In order for you to have a better experience, to improve our service, or to use it for any other purpose you agree to, we may collect information through service, subject to compliance with the relevant laws and regulations, to aggregate information or personalize it for our other services. For example, the information you gather when you use one of our services may be used to provide you with specific content in another service, or to show you relevant, non-generic push information. If we provide options in the relevant service, you can also authorize us to use the information provided and stored by that service for our other services

#### Information Security

We retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes stated in this privacy policy and as long as is required by law and regulation. We use a variety of security techniques and procedures to prevent loss of information, improper use, unauthorized access, or disclosure. For example, in some services, we will use encryption techniques, such as SSL, to protect the personal information you provide. But please understand that due to the limitations of technology and the possible existence of malicious means, in the internet industry, even if the best efforts to strengthen security measures, can not always guarantee 100% security information. You need to understand that the systems and communication networks you use to access our services may be affected by factors beyond our control.

#### Advertising services

We may use your relevant information to provide you with ads that are more relevant to you.

We may also use your information to send marketing messages to you through our services, e-mail, or other means to provide or promote our or third-party goods and services.

If you do not wish us to use your personal information for the purposes of the above-mentioned advertisement, you may use the relevant tips provided in our advertisement or the guidance provided in the specific service, request us to discontinue the use of your personal information for the above purposes.

#### Minors visiting our website

We encourage parents or guardians to direct minors under the age of 18 to use our services. We recommend that minors encourage their parents or guardians to read this privacy policy and that minors seek the consent and guidance of their parents or guardians before submitting personal information.

#### Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

* Google Adsense
* Outbrain
* Taboola
* **Snigel**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use various technologies to show the advertisements and some links that appear on BestRandoms. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

You can change your privacy settings by clicking the following button: Manage Consent.

BestRandoms has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. BestRandoms's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

#### The scope of the privacy policy

This privacy policy applies to all of our services except for certain specific services. These specific services will be subject to specific privacy policies. Specific privacy policies for certain services will specify more specifically how we use your information in those services. The privacy policy for this particular service forms part of the privacy policy. If there is any inconsistency between the privacy policy of a particular service and this privacy policy, the privacy policy of that particular service shall apply.

Please note that this privacy policy does not apply to:

Information collected by third-party services (including any third-party websites) accessed through our services;

Information is collected through other companies or agencies that advertise on our service.

#### Alternations

The provisions of the privacy policy may be revised in due course as part of the present privacy policy. If the changes result in a substantial reduction of your rights under this privacy policy, we will notify you of the changes by highlighting them on our home page or by e-mail or other means before they take effect. In that case, if you continue to use our services, you consent to be bound by the revised privacy policy.

Random Geographic Tools

Random Language Tools

Random Entertainment Tools

Random Name Tools

Random Nature Tools

Random People Tools

Random Team Tools

Random Profile Tools

×

#### Report a problem on this page

 Outdated content

 Wrong content

 Incomplete content

Copyright © 2024 BestRandoms.com All rights reserved.

[](http://statcounter.com/ "Web Analytics
Made Easy - StatCounter")
